One platform, countless insights

Get fast and easy access to customer insights at every step of their journey

#### Analytics

* [

    Product Analytics
    
    Understand the full user journey](https://amplitude.com/amplitude-analytics)
* [

    Web Analytics
    
    Get the metrics you need with one line of code](https://amplitude.com/web-analytics)
* [

    Session Replay
    
    Visualize sessions based on events in your product](https://amplitude.com/session-replay)
* [

    Warehouse-native Amplitude
    
    Unlock insights from your data warehouse](https://amplitude.com/warehouse-native)

#### Experiment

* [

    Feature Experimentation
    
    Innovate with personalized product experiences](https://amplitude.com/amplitude-experiment)
* [

    Web Experimentation
    
    Drive conversion with A/B testing powered by data](https://amplitude.com/web-experimentation)
* [

    Feature Management
    
    Build fast, target easily, and learn as you ship](https://amplitude.com/feature-management)

#### Data

* [

    Customer Data Platform
    
    Unite data across teams](https://amplitude.com/customer-data-platform)
* [

    Data Governance
    
    Complete data you can trust](https://amplitude.com/data-management)
* [

    Integrations
    
    Connect Amplitude to hundreds of partners](https://amplitude.com/integrations)
* [

    Security & Privacy
    
    Keep your data secure and compliant](https://amplitude.com/trust)
* [

    AI
    
    Self-service data meets self-service intelligence](https://amplitude.com/ai)

One platform, countless insights

Get fast and easy access to customer insights at every step of their journey

#### Analytics

* [

    Product Analytics
    
    Understand the full user journey](https://amplitude.com/amplitude-analytics)
* [

    Web Analytics
    
    Get the metrics you need with one line of code](https://amplitude.com/web-analytics)
* [

    Session Replay
    
    Visualize sessions based on events in your product](https://amplitude.com/session-replay)
* [

    Warehouse-native Amplitude
    
    Unlock insights from your data warehouse](https://amplitude.com/warehouse-native)

#### Experiment

* [

    Feature Experimentation
    
    Innovate with personalized product experiences](https://amplitude.com/amplitude-experiment)
* [

    Web Experimentation
    
    Drive conversion with A/B testing powered by data](https://amplitude.com/web-experimentation)
* [

    Feature Management
    
    Build fast, target easily, and learn as you ship](https://amplitude.com/feature-management)

#### Data

* [

    Customer Data Platform
    
    Unite data across teams](https://amplitude.com/customer-data-platform)
* [

    Data Governance
    
    Complete data you can trust](https://amplitude.com/data-management)
* [

    Integrations
    
    Connect Amplitude to hundreds of partners](https://amplitude.com/integrations)
* [

    Security & Privacy
    
    Keep your data secure and compliant](https://amplitude.com/trust)
* [

    AI
    
    Self-service data meets self-service intelligence](https://amplitude.com/ai)

Solutions that drive business results

Deliver customer value and drive business outcomes

#### Industry

* [

    Financial Services
    
    Personalize the banking experience](https://amplitude.com/industry/financial-services)
* [

    B2B
    
    Maximize product adoption](https://amplitude.com/industry/b2b-saas)
* [

    Media
    
    Identify impactful content](https://amplitude.com/industry/media)
* [

    Healthcare
    
    Simplify the digital healthcare experience](https://amplitude.com/industry/healthcare)
* [

    Ecommerce
    
    Optimize for transactions](https://amplitude.com/industry/ecommerce)

#### Use Case

* [

    Grow active users
    
    Get users hooked from day one](https://amplitude.com/solutions/user-acquisition)
* [

    Increase customer lifetime value
    
    Understand your customers like no one else](https://amplitude.com/solutions/retention)
* [

    Accelerate monetization
    
    Turn behavior into business](https://amplitude.com/solutions/monetization)

#### Team

* [

    Product
    
    Fuel faster growth](https://amplitude.com/solutions/product)
* [

    Data
    
    Make trusted data accessible](https://amplitude.com/solutions/data)
* [

    Engineering
    
    Ship faster, learn more](https://amplitude.com/solutions/engineering)
* [

    Marketing
    
    Build customers for life](https://amplitude.com/solutions/marketing)

#### Size

* [

    Startups
    
    Free analytics tools for startups](https://amplitude.com/startups)
* [

    Enterprise
    
    Advanced analytics for scaling businesses](https://amplitude.com/enterprise)

Solutions that drive business results

Deliver customer value and drive business outcomes

#### Industry

* [

    Financial Services
    
    Personalize the banking experience](https://amplitude.com/industry/financial-services)
* [

    B2B
    
    Maximize product adoption](https://amplitude.com/industry/b2b-saas)
* [

    Media
    
    Identify impactful content](https://amplitude.com/industry/media)
* [

    Healthcare
    
    Simplify the digital healthcare experience](https://amplitude.com/industry/healthcare)
* [

    Ecommerce
    
    Optimize for transactions](https://amplitude.com/industry/ecommerce)

#### Use Case

* [

    Grow active users
    
    Get users hooked from day one](https://amplitude.com/solutions/user-acquisition)
* [

    Increase customer lifetime value
    
    Understand your customers like no one else](https://amplitude.com/solutions/retention)
* [

    Accelerate monetization
    
    Turn behavior into business](https://amplitude.com/solutions/monetization)

#### Team

* [

    Product
    
    Fuel faster growth](https://amplitude.com/solutions/product)
* [

    Data
    
    Make trusted data accessible](https://amplitude.com/solutions/data)
* [

    Engineering
    
    Ship faster, learn more](https://amplitude.com/solutions/engineering)
* [

    Marketing
    
    Build customers for life](https://amplitude.com/solutions/marketing)

#### Size

* [

    Startups
    
    Free analytics tools for startups](https://amplitude.com/startups)
* [

    Enterprise
    
    Advanced analytics for scaling businesses](https://amplitude.com/enterprise)

#### Learn

* [

    Blog
    
    Thought leadership from industry experts](https://amplitude.com/blog)
* [

    Resource Center
    
    Expertise to guide your growth](https://amplitude.com/resources)
* [

    Glossary
    
    Learn about analytics, product, and technical terms](https://amplitude.com/glossary/terms)
* [

    Templates
    
    Amplitude template library](https://amplitude.com/templates)
* [

    Explore Hub
    
    Detailed guides on product and web analytics](https://amplitude.com/explore)

#### Connect

* [

    Community
    
    Connect with peers in product analytics](https://amplitude.com/community)
* [

    Events
    
    Register for live or virtual events](https://amplitude.com/events)
* [

    Customers
    
    Discover why customers love Amplitude](https://amplitude.com/customers)
* [

    Partners
    
    Accelerate business value through our ecosystem](https://amplitude.com/partners)

#### Support & Services

* [

    Help Center
    
    Answers to every Amplitude question](https://amplitude.com/docs)
* [

    Developer Hub
    
    Integrate and instrument Amplitude](https://www.docs.developers.amplitude.com/)
* [

    Academy & Training
    
    Become an Amplitude pro](https://academy.amplitude.com/)
* [

    Professional Services
    
    Drive business success with expert guidance and support](https://amplitude.com/services)

#### Tools

* [

    Benchmarks
    
    Understand how your product compares](https://amplitude.com/benchmarks)

#### Learn

* [

    Blog
    
    Thought leadership from industry experts](https://amplitude.com/blog)
* [

    Resource Center
    
    Expertise to guide your growth](https://amplitude.com/resources)
* [

    Glossary
    
    Learn about analytics, product, and technical terms](https://amplitude.com/glossary/terms)
* [

    Templates
    
    Amplitude template library](https://amplitude.com/templates)
* [

    Explore Hub
    
    Detailed guides on product and web analytics](https://amplitude.com/explore)

#### Connect

* [

    Community
    
    Connect with peers in product analytics](https://amplitude.com/community)
* [

    Events
    
    Register for live or virtual events](https://amplitude.com/events)
* [

    Customers
    
    Discover why customers love Amplitude](https://amplitude.com/customers)
* [

    Partners
    
    Accelerate business value through our ecosystem](https://amplitude.com/partners)

#### Support & Services

* [

    Help Center
    
    Answers to every Amplitude question](https://amplitude.com/docs)
* [

    Developer Hub
    
    Integrate and instrument Amplitude](https://www.docs.developers.amplitude.com/)
* [

    Academy & Training
    
    Become an Amplitude pro](https://academy.amplitude.com/)
* [

    Professional Services
    
    Drive business success with expert guidance and support](https://amplitude.com/services)

#### Tools

* [

    Benchmarks
    
    Understand how your product compares](https://amplitude.com/benchmarks)

One platform, countless insights

Get fast and easy access to customer insights at every step of their journey

#### Analytics

* [

    Product Analytics
    
    Understand the full user journey](https://amplitude.com/amplitude-analytics)
* [

    Web Analytics
    
    Get the metrics you need with one line of code](https://amplitude.com/web-analytics)
* [

    Session Replay
    
    Visualize sessions based on events in your product](https://amplitude.com/session-replay)
* [

    Warehouse-native Amplitude
    
    Unlock insights from your data warehouse](https://amplitude.com/warehouse-native)

#### Experiment

* [

    Feature Experimentation
    
    Innovate with personalized product experiences](https://amplitude.com/amplitude-experiment)
* [

    Web Experimentation
    
    Drive conversion with A/B testing powered by data](https://amplitude.com/web-experimentation)
* [

    Feature Management
    
    Build fast, target easily, and learn as you ship](https://amplitude.com/feature-management)

#### Data

* [

    Customer Data Platform
    
    Unite data across teams](https://amplitude.com/customer-data-platform)
* [

    Data Governance
    
    Complete data you can trust](https://amplitude.com/data-management)
* [

    Integrations
    
    Connect Amplitude to hundreds of partners](https://amplitude.com/integrations)
* [

    Security & Privacy
    
    Keep your data secure and compliant](https://amplitude.com/trust)
* [

    AI
    
    Self-service data meets self-service intelligence](https://amplitude.com/ai)

One platform, countless insights

Get fast and easy access to customer insights at every step of their journey

#### Analytics

* [

    Product Analytics
    
    Understand the full user journey](https://amplitude.com/amplitude-analytics)
* [

    Web Analytics
    
    Get the metrics you need with one line of code](https://amplitude.com/web-analytics)
* [

    Session Replay
    
    Visualize sessions based on events in your product](https://amplitude.com/session-replay)
* [

    Warehouse-native Amplitude
    
    Unlock insights from your data warehouse](https://amplitude.com/warehouse-native)

#### Experiment

* [

    Feature Experimentation
    
    Innovate with personalized product experiences](https://amplitude.com/amplitude-experiment)
* [

    Web Experimentation
    
    Drive conversion with A/B testing powered by data](https://amplitude.com/web-experimentation)
* [

    Feature Management
    
    Build fast, target easily, and learn as you ship](https://amplitude.com/feature-management)

#### Data

* [

    Customer Data Platform
    
    Unite data across teams](https://amplitude.com/customer-data-platform)
* [

    Data Governance
    
    Complete data you can trust](https://amplitude.com/data-management)
* [

    Integrations
    
    Connect Amplitude to hundreds of partners](https://amplitude.com/integrations)
* [

    Security & Privacy
    
    Keep your data secure and compliant](https://amplitude.com/trust)
* [

    AI
    
    Self-service data meets self-service intelligence](https://amplitude.com/ai)

Solutions that drive business results

Deliver customer value and drive business outcomes

#### Industry

* [

    Financial Services
    
    Personalize the banking experience](https://amplitude.com/industry/financial-services)
* [

    B2B
    
    Maximize product adoption](https://amplitude.com/industry/b2b-saas)
* [

    Media
    
    Identify impactful content](https://amplitude.com/industry/media)
* [

    Healthcare
    
    Simplify the digital healthcare experience](https://amplitude.com/industry/healthcare)
* [

    Ecommerce
    
    Optimize for transactions](https://amplitude.com/industry/ecommerce)

#### Use Case

* [

    Grow active users
    
    Get users hooked from day one](https://amplitude.com/solutions/user-acquisition)
* [

    Increase customer lifetime value
    
    Understand your customers like no one else](https://amplitude.com/solutions/retention)
* [

    Accelerate monetization
    
    Turn behavior into business](https://amplitude.com/solutions/monetization)

#### Team

* [

    Product
    
    Fuel faster growth](https://amplitude.com/solutions/product)
* [

    Data
    
    Make trusted data accessible](https://amplitude.com/solutions/data)
* [

    Engineering
    
    Ship faster, learn more](https://amplitude.com/solutions/engineering)
* [

    Marketing
    
    Build customers for life](https://amplitude.com/solutions/marketing)

#### Size

* [

    Startups
    
    Free analytics tools for startups](https://amplitude.com/startups)
* [

    Enterprise
    
    Advanced analytics for scaling businesses](https://amplitude.com/enterprise)

Solutions that drive business results

Deliver customer value and drive business outcomes

#### Industry

* [

    Financial Services
    
    Personalize the banking experience](https://amplitude.com/industry/financial-services)
* [

    B2B
    
    Maximize product adoption](https://amplitude.com/industry/b2b-saas)
* [

    Media
    
    Identify impactful content](https://amplitude.com/industry/media)
* [

    Healthcare
    
    Simplify the digital healthcare experience](https://amplitude.com/industry/healthcare)
* [

    Ecommerce
    
    Optimize for transactions](https://amplitude.com/industry/ecommerce)

#### Use Case

* [

    Grow active users
    
    Get users hooked from day one](https://amplitude.com/solutions/user-acquisition)
* [

    Increase customer lifetime value
    
    Understand your customers like no one else](https://amplitude.com/solutions/retention)
* [

    Accelerate monetization
    
    Turn behavior into business](https://amplitude.com/solutions/monetization)

#### Team

* [

    Product
    
    Fuel faster growth](https://amplitude.com/solutions/product)
* [

    Data
    
    Make trusted data accessible](https://amplitude.com/solutions/data)
* [

    Engineering
    
    Ship faster, learn more](https://amplitude.com/solutions/engineering)
* [

    Marketing
    
    Build customers for life](https://amplitude.com/solutions/marketing)

#### Size

* [

    Startups
    
    Free analytics tools for startups](https://amplitude.com/startups)
* [

    Enterprise
    
    Advanced analytics for scaling businesses](https://amplitude.com/enterprise)

#### Learn

* [

    Blog
    
    Thought leadership from industry experts](https://amplitude.com/blog)
* [

    Resource Center
    
    Expertise to guide your growth](https://amplitude.com/resources)
* [

    Glossary
    
    Learn about analytics, product, and technical terms](https://amplitude.com/glossary/terms)
* [

    Templates
    
    Amplitude template library](https://amplitude.com/templates)
* [

    Explore Hub
    
    Detailed guides on product and web analytics](https://amplitude.com/explore)

#### Connect

* [

    Community
    
    Connect with peers in product analytics](https://amplitude.com/community)
* [

    Events
    
    Register for live or virtual events](https://amplitude.com/events)
* [

    Customers
    
    Discover why customers love Amplitude](https://amplitude.com/customers)
* [

    Partners
    
    Accelerate business value through our ecosystem](https://amplitude.com/partners)

#### Support & Services

* [

    Help Center
    
    Answers to every Amplitude question](https://amplitude.com/docs)
* [

    Developer Hub
    
    Integrate and instrument Amplitude](https://www.docs.developers.amplitude.com/)
* [

    Academy & Training
    
    Become an Amplitude pro](https://academy.amplitude.com/)
* [

    Professional Services
    
    Drive business success with expert guidance and support](https://amplitude.com/services)

#### Tools

* [

    Benchmarks
    
    Understand how your product compares](https://amplitude.com/benchmarks)

#### Learn

* [

    Blog
    
    Thought leadership from industry experts](https://amplitude.com/blog)
* [

    Resource Center
    
    Expertise to guide your growth](https://amplitude.com/resources)
* [

    Glossary
    
    Learn about analytics, product, and technical terms](https://amplitude.com/glossary/terms)
* [

    Templates
    
    Amplitude template library](https://amplitude.com/templates)
* [

    Explore Hub
    
    Detailed guides on product and web analytics](https://amplitude.com/explore)

#### Connect

* [

    Community
    
    Connect with peers in product analytics](https://amplitude.com/community)
* [

    Events
    
    Register for live or virtual events](https://amplitude.com/events)
* [

    Customers
    
    Discover why customers love Amplitude](https://amplitude.com/customers)
* [

    Partners
    
    Accelerate business value through our ecosystem](https://amplitude.com/partners)

#### Support & Services

* [

    Help Center
    
    Answers to every Amplitude question](https://amplitude.com/docs)
* [

    Developer Hub
    
    Integrate and instrument Amplitude](https://www.docs.developers.amplitude.com/)
* [

    Academy & Training
    
    Become an Amplitude pro](https://academy.amplitude.com/)
* [

    Professional Services
    
    Drive business success with expert guidance and support](https://amplitude.com/services)

#### Tools

* [

    Benchmarks
    
    Understand how your product compares](https://amplitude.com/benchmarks)

Privacy Notice
==============

Table of Contents

* 1\. Introduction
    
* 2\. What This Privacy Notice Covers
    
* 3\. Personal Data We Collect And How We Use The Personal Data
    
* 4\. When Amplitude Discloses Personal Data
    
* 5\. Customer End User Data
    
* 6\. International Transfer
    
* 7\. Our Commitment To Data Security
    
* 8\. Your Choices About How We Use And Disclose Information We Collect From You
    
* 9\. Other Information About Our Privacy Practices
    
* 10\. Updates And Changes To The Privacy Notice
    
* 11\. Disputes
    
* 12\. California Privacy Rights
    
* 13\. Contact Us
    
* 14\. Cookies
    
* 15\. Previous Privacy Version

**Last Updated: September 26, 2023**

1\. Introduction
----------------

Amplitude, Inc. ("**Amplitude**," "**we**," or "**us**") is a cloud-based product-analytics platform that helps customers build better products. Amplitude respects the privacy of individuals and is committed to protecting the information of visitors to the website ("**Visitors**") and individuals or entities that register to use the Amplitude products and services ("**Customers**"). This Privacy Notice describes Amplitude’s practices for collecting, storing, using, disclosing, and otherwise processing information in relation to Visitors of the website, amplitude.com, including our Community Forum and Amplitude Academy ("**Website**"), Amplitude’s marketing activities, and Customers accessing and using our products and services (collectively, "**Product**").

Please read the following carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information collected through the Website, through your use of the Product, and through our marketing activities. If you do not agree with the below policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website or register to use our Product, or to unsubscribe from our marketing.

2\. What This Privacy Notice Covers
-----------------------------------

This Privacy Notice covers how we treat Personal Data that we gather about you in the course of our business, including when you access or use our Website or Product and through our or our partner’s events and marketing activities. Specifically, Amplitude is the controller of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Notice, when it collects personal information from: (i) Visitors to Amplitude’s publicly available Website; (ii) Customers and their employees or other authorized users of their Amplitude instance when registering to use and using the Product; and (iii) when we receive personal information from or about you through our sales and marketing activities or events.

Throughout this Privacy Notice, "Personal Data" means any information that identifies or relates to a particular individual and also includes information referred to as "personally identifiable information" or "personal information" under applicable data privacy laws, rules or regulations.

For clarity, this Privacy Notice does not apply to Customer End User Data (as defined below) submitted by our customers to the Product. In those circumstances, Amplitude is processing Customer End User Data on behalf of that customer and that customer is responsible for the collection and use of your data. In addition, this Privacy Notice does not apply to the mobile applications, websites or services offered by our Customers or other third-parties. You should refer to that customer’s or third party’s privacy notice and direct any inquiries to them.

3\. Personal Data We Collect And How We Use The Personal Data
-------------------------------------------------------------

**3.1** **PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT**

**The Personal Data you provide to us directly**

* You provide your Personal Data to us when you voluntarily fill in forms on our Website such as when you request a demo or to contact sales. This Personal Data may include: first and last name, company name, job title, work email address, country and/or state, phone number and the content of your request.
* You may also share Personal Data with us through our Website when you register for an event or online webinar or training; sign up to receive our newsletter; subscribe to our blog; register to contribute and participate in our Community Forum or use Amplitude Academy; download a white paper or playbook; or complete a survey. This Personal Data may include: first and last name, company name, job title, work email address, country and/or state, phone number and the content of your request.
* In order to access and use the Product, you are required to register for an account with us. When you register for an account, you may provide Personal Data to us, including first and last name, company name, job title, work email address, country and/or state, phone number, and username and password.
* You may also provide Amplitude with your personal information at a marketing event or through marketing activities. This Personal Data may include: first and last name, company name, job title, work email address, work address, phone number and the content of your request.
* If you attend an in-person or virtual event or agree to be recorded in a telephone or video meeting, we may record some or all of that event or meeting. For events, we may also document the event by taking photos or interviewing you at the event. We use this information for business and marketing purposes and training purposes.
* You may choose to participate in an Amplitude program that allows you to pay fees with a credit or debit card, in which case you may provide your credit card or other payment details information directly to our third party payment processor. As explained below, Amplitude does not store this information.

**The Personal Data we collect from third party sources**

Amplitude may obtain Personal Data about you from third parties, including, but not limited to, marketing event organizers, partners, resellers, and public databases and websites.

* _Service providers_. For example, we may use third party providers of business contact information. The Personal Data provided to Amplitude by these Service providers about you may include your first and last name, company name, job title, business mailing addresses, business email addresses and business phone numbers, and LinkedIn URLs for purposes of delivering relevant Product updates and information, email content, advertisements and events.
* _Advertising partners._ We receive information about you from some of our service providers who assist us with marketing or promotional services, related to how you interact with our Website, event promotions, advertisements or communications. Amplitude requires that any third party providing us with Personal Data contact information has obtained the information lawfully and has the appropriate consent to share the information with Amplitude.
* _Google’s API Services._ Amplitude integrates Google’s Application Programming Interface (API) Services to allow users the option of logging into our platform with their Google credentials. If you choose to login to the Amplitude platform with Google’s API services, Google may share with us your email, name, and your unique Google ID so we can identify and authenticate you as a user. We do not share your data with any other parties, other than as may be necessary to provide our services to you. Amplitude’s use of information received from Google’s APIs will adhere to the [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy).

**Targeted Online Advertisements:**

We use third party service providers to help us understand our marketing efforts and to reach potential customers across the web. These third parties may use targeting and advertising cookies to track your online activity and across different channels, including our websites, email, and other websites and applications, to understand your interests, to display an advertisement for Amplitude, or email you with a marketing communication for Amplitude.

This Privacy Notice does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies in third party ads. You should check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn more about their use of cookies and your information.

**Information We Collect Automatically:**

* As you navigate through and interact with our Website or Product, we may use cookies, which are small files placed on your computer or mobile device, and web beacons, which are small electronic files located on pages of the Website or in email communications, to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and events, and patterns. You can learn more about cookies and how we use them [here](#chapters-content-14).
* We also use cookies to access information when you sign in, store your preferences, interact with certain functionality in the Product, to keep you logged in, and to store a limited amount of behavioral data.
* The data automatically collected from cookies and web beacons may include information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language) and details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, logs about your login history, identity confirmation, page views, length of visit and website navigation paths as well as information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address and connecting software. We collect this data in order to help us provide, support and improve our Website, the Product and the user experience with our Website and Product, and for network and information security purposes. You can learn more about cookies and how we use them [here](#chapters-content-15).
* Additionally, Amplitude may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about our Customers' interactions with the Product in a manner that allows us to reproduce and fix issues and to identify areas of improvement for our Product. Customers can opt out of the use of this software during their use of the Product by contacting us at privacy@amplitude.com.
* The information we collect automatically may also include statistical and performance information arising from our Customers’ use of our Product and Visitors to our Website. This type of data will only be used by us in an aggregated and anonymized manner.

**3.2** **THE WAY AMPLITUDE USES YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

We use Personal Data that we collect about you or that you provide to us as is necessary to run our business and to carry out day-to-day business activities. How we use the Personal Data we collect depends in part on how you choose to communicate with us, how you use our Website and/or Product and interact with us, and any preferences you have communicated to us. In general, we use the Personal Data in order to respond to a request from you, to carry out our legal obligations, to fulfill a contract with you, to provide the Product or other services to you, to make improvements to the Product, to protect your vital interests, to provide you with notices and for other purposes with your consent as described below.

* We use the Personal Data you provide to us when you fill in forms on our Website to respond to your request, provide requested information, and to contact you about that request. Our legal basis for processing this personal information is our legitimate interest in communicating with you and fulfilling your requests.
* We may use your Personal Data to provide the Product to you, including to make improvements to the Product and understand your preferences to personalize your experience, as well as for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major changes to the Website, the Product or for customer service purposes). Our legal basis for processing this Personal Data is in the performance of our contract to provide the Product or other services to you.
* We also use the Personal Data you provide to us for the purpose of operating our Website and Product; to detect bugs, report errors and to maintain the quality and safety of our Website and Product; and for ensuring the security and integrity of our Website and Product. Our legal basis for processing this personal information is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of and security of our Website and Product.
* For Personal Data that we collect through tracking technologies about your interaction with our Website and Product, we use this information for analyzing the use of the Website and Product in order to improve the quality and design, user experience, and performance of our Website and Product. Our legal basis for processing this type of data is our legitimate interests, namely, to provide you with a better user experience.
* For Personal Data we collect through targeted or online advertising cookies, we use this information to display and measure engagement with advertisements across different devices and sites and to serve you with marketing materials.
* We may use the Personal Data you provide to us at marketing events, when you register for an online webinar or download a whitepaper for the purpose of offering, marketing and selling products and services to you or to communicate with you about an event. Our legal basis for processing this Personal Data is consent, which you can withdraw at any time.
* We may also use any of your Personal Data identified in this Privacy Notice for the purposes of: (i) enforcing our agreements and policies, including Terms of Service or Main Service Agreement, (ii) protecting or defending Amplitude’s legal rights; (iv) protecting your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person; or (v) complying with a legal obligation.
* We may use your Personal Data for any other business purpose stated when collecting your Personal Data or as otherwise set forth in applicable data privacy laws.

We will not collect additional categories of Personal Data or use the Personal Data we collect for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice.

As noted in the list above, we may communicate with you if you’ve provided us the means to do so. For example, if you’ve given us your email address, we may send you promotional email offers or email you about your use of the Product or Website. Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us, which helps us improve our Website and Product. If you do not want to receive communications from us, you can unsubscribe from marketing communications or email us with your preferences at privacy@amplitude.com or ccpa@amplitude.com.

**3.3 LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL DATA FOR EEA, UK, AND SWISS VISITORS AND CUSTOMERS**

If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (“**EEA**”), United Kingdom, Switzerland, or another relevant jurisdiction, we collect and process Personal Data about you only where we have a legal basis or bases for doing so under applicable laws. The legal bases depend on how you use the Website and/or Product, the Product your organization has purchased or uses, how you choose to interact and communicate with Amplitude’s Website and Product, and whether you attend Amplitude events. However, we will collect Personal Data only where we have your consent to do so, where we need the Personal Data to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect Personal Data from you and we will endeavor to make that clear at collection.

4\. When Amplitude Discloses Personal Data
------------------------------------------

We may disclose Personal Data that we collect or you provide to us as described below.

* We may disclose Personal Data that we collect or you provide to us to our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* We may share your Personal Data collected from you as described in this Privacy Notice with third-party service providers who need to access the Personal Data in order to perform services on behalf of Amplitude, such as processing or storing such information, securing our Website or Product, or providing analytics services on our behalf. The third-party service providers are limited to using the Personal Data solely to provide the services to us and are bound by contractual obligations to keep Personal Data confidential and secure and to use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
* If you are part of an Amplitude program that allows you to pay fees with a credit card or debit card and you choose to pay such fees with a credit card or debit card, your credit card or debit card information is provided directly to our third-party payment processor, Stripe, to process the payments. The payment information is transmitted directly via an encrypted connection to Stripe. Stripe uses, processes and stores your Personal Data and payment information in accordance with Stripe’s privacy policy available at stripe.com/us/privacy. Amplitude does not collect or store your payment information. Stripe maintains that it is PCI compliant and you can learn more about Stripe’s security measures available at stripe.com/help/security.
* We may share your Personal Data if we believe disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable laws, regulations, respond to a court order, subpoena or a government request (such as a search warrant). If a government request or other legal process requires Amplitude to disclose your personal data, then Amplitude will use reasonable efforts to provide you with prior notification of the disclosure unless Amplitude is prohibited by law from doing so.
* Amplitude also reserves the right to disclose your Personal Data that Amplitude believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to: (i) enforce our agreements and policies, including for billing and collection purposes, (ii) protect the security or integrity of the Website or Product; or (iii) protect or defend Amplitude’s legal rights.
* In the event that Amplitude is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign your Personal Data as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.
* Amplitude may disclose anonymized and/or aggregated information about Visitors to the Website or our Customers’ use of the Product that does not identify any individual.
* Amplitude makes available our Community Forum and other resources or materials where you may post user generated content. The information you choose to post is publicly available and may be read and collected by others that visit these sections of the Website. Except for the details in your profile (e.g., username), the categories of data disclosed in these circumstances will depend on what information you choose to provide.
* Amplitude may disclose Personal Data to third-party business partners at your direction, if you access or request contact from the third-party business partners through the Product or Website or at a marketing event.
* Amplitude may disclose Personal Data that we collect or you provide to us for any purpose disclosed by us when we collect the information or with your consent, such as advertising or marketing providers.

5\. Customer End User Data
--------------------------

**This Privacy Notice does not apply to Customer End Users, Customer End User Data or Customer Applications.** With respect to the Personal Data collected by our Customers and submitted to the Amplitude platform, Amplitude is a processor and only processes such Personal Data in accordance with the instructions of our Customers. Our Customers may integrate into their mobile applications, websites or other services (collectively, "**Customer Applications**") certain aspects of our Product in order to understand how their own users ("**Customer End Users**") engage with the Customer Applications ("**Customer End User Data**").

Our Customers, not Amplitude, choose the type of Customer End User Data collected by Customer Applications, and submitted and processed through our Customers’ use of the Products. We process the Customer End User Data only according to the instructions of Customers and our legal obligations with respect to the Customer End User Data is set forth in the agreement between us and our Customers. The collection of Customer End User Data through Customer Applications is governed by our Customers’ privacy policies, and if you are a Customer End User then you should review the Customer’s privacy policy to learn more about the Customer’s data handling practices.

While Amplitude recognizes that an individual has the right to access, delete and amend the data collected about that individual, Amplitude only has a relationship with our Customers and does not interact with the Customer End Users. As such, if you are a Customer End User and you would like to access, amend or delete your data, you need to contact the Customer directly with your request which Customer may process. Amplitude will respond within a reasonable period of time to any such request or assistance requested by our Customer.

Amplitude only retains the Customer End User Data we process on behalf of our Customers for as long as necessary to provide the Product to our Customers or as required to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce any agreement.

6\. International Transfer
--------------------------

By interacting with the Website or using the Product or otherwise providing information to Amplitude, you understand that your Personal Data may be transferred to the United States or another country other than your country of residence and you consent to such transfer. In order to ensure that your Personal Data receives an adequate level of protection and security, Amplitude has implemented appropriate safeguards for cross-border transfers of Personal Data, as required by applicable data protection laws. These safeguards may include using the European Commission-approved standard contractual clauses to protect the transfer of your Personal Data to Amplitude’s corporate affiliates or service providers, if required by applicable law.

Amplitude complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (“EU-U.S. DPF”), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (“Swiss-U.S. DPF”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Amplitude has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. DPF Principles with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. Amplitude has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles (together, the “DPF Principles”), the DPF Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (“DPF”) program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/).

For the actions of third party agents Amplitude engages to process data on our behalf, Amplitude remains responsible and liable under the DPF Principles if a third party agent processes the Personal Data in a manner inconsistent with the DPF Principles, unless Amplitude proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

7\. Our Commitment To Data Security
-----------------------------------

Amplitude uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards designed to secure your Personal Data from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. These measures include, for example, physical access controls, encryption, firewalls, and detection and monitoring. Our personnel who may have access to your Personal Data are required to keep that information confidential and trained on their security and privacy obligations.

You, however, are also responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and other information used by you to access the Website or use the Product. While Amplitude does its best to protect your Personal Data, any transmission of your Personal Data is done at your own risk and Amplitude cannot guarantee that such Personal Data may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Except as expressly required by law, we are not responsible for the theft, destruction, loss or inadvertent disclosure of your Personal Data or information. If Amplitude learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Amplitude may post a notice on the Website or in Product if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

8\. Your Choices About How We Use And Disclose Information We Collect From You
------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We strive to provide you with choices regarding your Personal Data and we understand that you have the right to access, correct, delete, object to and restrict our use of your Personal Data. We also understand that you have the right to obtain a copy of your Personal Data from us and to withdraw your consent to the processing of your Personal Data by us. Please note that the rights set forth in this Section 8, unless otherwise noted, apply globally to all Visitors and Customers, whether or not you are a California resident or a resident of the EEA, United Kingdom, or Switzerland. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your Personal Data:

* You may choose not to provide Personal Data through our Website or when you register for the Product, in which case Amplitude may not be able to provide certain services to you or respond to your requests.
* You can access, review, correct and/or change your Personal Data by logging into your account on the Website or Product and visiting your account profile page. You may also send us an email at privacy@amplitude.com or ccpa@amplitude.com to request access to, correct or delete any Personal Data that you have provided to us. In some cases, we may not be able to delete your Personal Data except by also deleting your user account.
* If you do not wish to have your email address or other contact information used by us to promote our own products or services, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your Personal Data, by updating your user or subscription preferences in your account profile(s), or by sending us an email stating your request to privacy@amplitude.com. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may unsubscribe to receive future emails via the unsubscribe link in that email or adjust your user preferences in your account profile as noted above. The opt out specified above does not apply to information provided to us as a result of a purchase, product service experience or other transactions. You cannot unsubscribe from non-promotional and transactional communications.
* You may also request a copy of your Personal Data that you have provided to us directly by sending an email to privacy@amplitude.com or ccpa@amplitude.com. We will provide you a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic form.
* If we collected and processed your Personal Data with your consent, where required by law, you can withdraw your consent at any time by emailing privacy@amplitude.com or ccpa@amplitude.com.
* Depending on your country or state of residence, including if you are a California resident, you have the right to opt out of the sale of Personal Data, certain sharing of Personal Data with third party ad partners, and the right to limit the use or disclosure of sensitive personal information. We do not sell your Personal Data or use or disclose sensitive personal information for purposes other than those permitted by the CCPA. We may share Personal Data with third party ad partners, such as through cookies or by providing lists of email addresses for potential customers so we can reach them across the web with relevant ads. If you wish to opt out of sharing, you may adjust your preferences in the Cookie Settings.
* If you wish to opt out of this sharing of your Personal Data with cookies on this domain, please update your Cookie Settings.

Please note to exercise the rights set forth above we may ask you to: (1) provide sufficient information to allow us to verify that you are the person about whom we have collected Personal Data, and (2) describe the request in sufficient detail to allow us to understand, evaluate, and respond to it. Each request that meets both of these criteria will be considered a "Valid Request." We may not respond to requests that do not meet these criteria. We will only use Personal Data provided in a Valid Request to verify you and complete your request. You do not need an account to submit a Valid Request.

We will work to respond to your Valid Request within 30 days of receipt. We will not charge you a fee for making a Valid Request unless your Valid Request(s) is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that your Valid Request warrants a fee, we will notify you of the fee and explain that decision before completing your request.

You may submit a Valid Request, or appeal our response to a valid request, by emailing us at privacy@amplitude.com or ccpa@amplitude.com with the appropriate information and detail.

We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights under the GDPR, CCPA or other applicable data privacy laws or regulations. We will not deny you our goods or services, charge you different prices or rates, or provide you a lower quality of goods and services if you exercise your rights under the GDPR, CCPA or other applicable data privacy laws or regulations.

9\. Other Information About Our Privacy Practices
-------------------------------------------------

**9.1** **Our Retention Practices**

Personal Data that Amplitude collects and processes as a controller for the purposes identified in this Privacy Notice are not kept by Amplitude for longer than is necessary for the specific purpose identified in this Privacy Notice, unless required to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your Personal Data to comply with applicable laws or regulations), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. When we no longer have a legitimate business need to retain your Personal Data, we will either delete or anonymize it.

**9.2** **Children’s Privacy**

Amplitude’s Website and Product are not directed at children. We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Data directly from individuals that are under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not provide or send us any Personal Data or attempt to register for or otherwise use the Product. If we learn that a child under 13 has directly provided us with their Personal Data through the Website or Product, or that we have collected information for a child under 13 through our marketing activities, then we will delete that information. If you believe a child under 13 has registered for an account on the Website or Product, or is receiving marketing materials from Amplitude, please contact us at privacy@amplitude.com.

**9.3** **Automated Decision-Making**

Amplitude does not use any Personal Data provided by you for the purpose of automated decision-making or profiling.

**9.4** **Other Websites; Links**

Our Website, Product or marketing materials may contain links to other third party websites or applications (such as Facebook, LinkedIn or Twitter). This Privacy Notice does not apply to any third party websites, including through any application that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website or Product, and Amplitude is not responsible for the privacy policies and the content of the third party websites or applications.

10\. Updates And Changes To The Privacy Notice
----------------------------------------------

Please note that we reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Notice, to reflect changes in our practices, technologies, additional factors, and to be consistent with applicable data protection and privacy laws or other legal requirements. The modified Privacy Notice will be posted on this website along with the effective date. If, in our reasonable discretion, the changes are material, we will provide you with additional notice (such as adding a notice on our Website, in the Product, or sending you an email notification). Changes to this Privacy Notice are effective when they are posted on this page.

11\. Disputes
-------------

As part of our commitment to the DPF Principles, if you are a resident of the European Union, UK, or Switzerland and you have a privacy or data use concern, please contact Amplitude directly at privacy@amplitude.com and Amplitude will use its best efforts to address your concern within 45 days of receipt of your complaint. For an unresolved privacy or data use concern that Amplitude has not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S. based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at [https://www.jamsadr.com/DPF-Dispute-Resolution](https://www.jamsadr.com/DPF-Dispute-Resolution).  
  
For any DPF disputes that cannot be resolved by the methods above, you may be able to invoke a binding arbitration process under certain conditions. To find out more about the DPF's binding arbitration scheme, please see Annex I of the DPF Principles, here: [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/Participation-Requirements-Data-Privacy-Framework-DPF-Principles-dpf](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/Participation-Requirements-Data-Privacy-Framework-DPF-Principles-dpf).

The Federal Trade Commission has investigation and enforcement authority over Amplitude’s compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF

12\. California Privacy Rights
------------------------------

Under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 and its amendments (“CCPA”), California residents have certain rights to disclosures about how we collect, use, retain and disclose your Personal Data. This section addresses those requirements. For a description of all of our data collection, use and disclosure practices, please read this Privacy Notice in its entirety.  
  
**Personal Data Collection and Disclosure**  
  
Amplitude does not sell Personal Data as we understand the term “sell” to be defined by the CCPA. We share Personal Data, as we understand the term “share” to be defined by the CCPA, as set forth below.  
  
The categories of Personal Data we may collect from you, from third parties, and from your interactions with us, and categories of third party recipients to whom we disclose such Personal Data for business purposes are set forth below. For additional detail about the Personal Data we collect and use and with whom we share this Personal Data and for what purpose, please review Sections 3 and 4 above.

| Categories of Personal Data We Collect | Categories of Third Party Recipients to Whom We Disclose Personal Data for Business Purposes |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers (such as name, email address, work address, and phone number) | Service providers; third parties |
| Commercial information (such as account records and transaction data) | Service providers; third parties |
| Internet or other network or device activity (such as browsing history or Website or Product usage) | Service providers |
| Geolocation data (such as country, city, or approximate location inferred from your IP address) | Service providers |
| Professional or employment-related data | Service providers; third parties |

The following categories of Personal Data have been shared in the preceding 12 months with third party advertising partners and advertising technology providers so that we can reach you with advertisements for our products and services and make them more relevant to you:

* Identifiers and contact information
* Analytics or other electronic network activity.

Amplitude does not use or disclose sensitive personal information for purposes other than those permitted purposes under the CCPA. Amplitude does not have actual knowledge that it sells or shares Personal Data of individuals under the age of 16.  
  
We retain Personal Data as described in Section 9.1 above.  
  
California law gives California residents the right to make certain requests with regard to their Personal Data. Please see Section 8 for a description of your choices and how you may make a request.

13\. Contact Us
---------------

If you have any comments, concerns or questions about this Privacy Notice or our privacy practices in general, please send an email to [privacy@amplitude.com](mailto:privacy@amplitude.com), [ccpa@amplitude.com](mailto:ccpa@amplitude.com), or send mail to:

Amplitude, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
201 Third Street, Suite 200  
San Francisco, CA 94103

**  
EFFECTIVE DATE**

This Privacy Notice was last updated on September 26, 2023.

14\. Cookies
------------

Amplitude uses cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns. Below we describe what cookies and web beacons are, why we use cookies and web beacons, the types of cookies and web beacons that we use, as well as what you can do in order to manage and delete cookies and web beacons.

**What are cookies and web beacons?**

* Cookies are small text files that websites often store on computer hard drives or mobile devices of visitors to their websites. A cookie contains a unique number, which is used to recognize your computer or mobile device when you return to our Website. Cookies can remain on your computer or mobile device for different periods of time. The cookies can be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies. Persistent cookies are stored by a web browser and remain valid until a set expiration date. Session cookies only exist while your internet browser is open and are automatically deleted once you close your browser.
* Web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) are small electronic files contained on pages of websites that permit companies to count users who have visited certain webpages on a website and are used for other related website statistics (e.g., recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

**What does Amplitude** **use cookies and web beacons for?**

Amplitude uses a variety of cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies for different purposes. Specifically, Amplitude uses cookies and web beacons to enhance the experience of our visitors to our Website (for example, by remembering your preferences and letting you navigate between pages efficiently) and to better understand how the Website and Product are used. Cookies may tell us, for example, whether you have visited the Website before or whether you are a new visitor.

**What types of cookies and web beacons are used by Amplitude?**

Amplitude uses both first-party and third-party cookies and web beacons. First-party cookies and web beacons are cookies and web beacons that are served directly by Amplitude to your computer or mobile device. Third-party cookies and web beacons are served by a third-party service provider on behalf of Amplitude. Third-party cookies are most commonly used for advertising and analytics purposes.

There are four categories of cookies and web beacons used by Amplitude. Specifically, Amplitude uses essential, performance, functionality and advertising cookies and web beacons.

* Essential cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies are necessary for the operation of the Website and Product. These tracking technologies enable you to move around on the Website and use the Website’s features. You may not opt-out of these types of cookies because they are required to operate the Website and Product.
* Performance cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies collect information about how you have used the Website and Product. We use performance cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies to improve the user experience with our Website and Product.
* Functionality cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies allow us to remember how you are logged into our Website, when you logged in or out and the actions you have taken while you have been logged into the Website.
* Advertising cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies are used by our third-party service providers to deliver advertising to you on other third-party websites as well as help measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns. We also use these types of cookies to analyze Website visits and ad conversions from third-party websites.

The table below lists the types of cookies and third party service providers currently used by Amplitude but may not include all cookies or third party service providers. In addition, the below list of cookies and third party service providers is subject to change at any time.

| Cookie Type | Who serves it | What it does | More information |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Performance | Amplitude | We use our own products and services to analyze the user behavior within our website and our own products and services. | For more information about our privacy practices, see [https://amplitude.com/privacy](https://amplitude.com/privacy) |
| Performance | Google Analytics | We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. | For more information about Google’s privacy practices, see [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) |
| Functional | Intercom | We use Intercom to power chat functionality. | For more information about Intercom’s privacy practices, see [https://www.intercom.com/legal/privacy](https://www.intercom.com/legal/privacy) |
| Advertising | Marketo | We use Marketo for marketing automation services. | For more information about Marketo’s cookie policy, see [https://documents.marketo.com/legal/cookies/](https://documents.marketo.com/legal/cookies/) |
| Advertising | Doubleclick | We use Doubleclick to track advertisements and measure website visits and conversions. | For more information about opting out of the ads, see [https://adssettings.google.com/u/0/authenticated](https://adssettings.google.com/u/0/authenticated) |
| Advertising | LinkedIn | We use LinkedIn to track conversions and website visits from our advertisements displayed on LinkedIn. | For more information about LinkedIn’s privacy practices, please see [https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy) |
| Advertising | Facebook | We use Facebook to track conversions and website visits from our advertisements displayed on Facebook. | For more information about Facebook’s privacy practices, please see [https://www.facebook.com/help/www/213802165366955](https://www.facebook.com/help/www/213802165366955) |
| Advertising | AddThis | We use AddThis for their website tools like social sharing buttons. | For more information about AddThis’s privacy practices, please see [https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/addthis-privacy-policy.html](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/addthis-privacy-policy.html) |
| Advertising | StackAdapt | We use StackAdapt to track advertisements and measure website visits and conversions. | For more information about StackAdapt’s privacy practices, please see [https://www.stackadapt.com/platform-and-services-privacy-policy](https://www.stackadapt.com/platform-and-services-privacy-policy) |
| Advertising | Bing | We use Bing to track conversions and website visits from our advertisements displayed on Bing. | For more information about Bing’s privacy practices, please see [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement) |
| Advertising | Reddit | We use Reddit to track conversions and website visits from our advertisements displayed on Reddit. | For more information about Reddit’s privacy practices, please see [https://www.reddit.com/policies/privacy-policy](https://www.reddit.com/policies/privacy-policy) |

**What are your choices about cookies?**

You can decide whether or not to accept cookies through our Cookie Settings link on our Website. Most browsers allow you to configure the browser settings so that cookies from websites cannot be placed on your computer or mobile device. If you choose not to accept cookies, then you may be able to continue browsing our Website but we may not be able to provide you with certain features. If you want to opt out of advertising or performance cookies, then you may do so by reviewing the privacy policies of the third party service providers who serve the advertising and performance cookies identified above. If you would like further information about cookies and how to manage and delete them, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

You can also delete all cookies that are already on your computer. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and the Product, Website and functionalities may not work.

**What are your choices about cookies and interest-based advertisements?**

Through the Digital Advertising Alliance and Network Advertising Initiative, several media and marketing associations have developed an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of, and greater control over, ads that are customized based on a consumer’s online behavior across different websites and properties. To make choices about internet-based ads from participating third parties, including to opt-out of receiving behaviorally targeted advertisements from participating organizations or to learn more about opting out of advertising cookies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s or Digital Advertising Alliance’s consumer opt-out pages, which are located at [http://networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://networkadvertising.org/choices/) or [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). For those users located in the European Union, you can visit the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s user information website a [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

15\. Previous Privacy Version
-----------------------------

Platform

Resources

Support

Partners

Company

[Terms of Service](https://amplitude.com/terms)[Privacy Notice](https://amplitude.com/privacy)[Acceptable Use Policy](https://amplitude.com/aup)[Legal](https://amplitude.com/legal)Cookie Settings[JP (日本語)](https://amplitude.jp/)

© 2024 Amplitude, Inc. All rights reserved. Amplitude is a registered trademark of Amplitude, Inc.
